你到底想怎么样  德洛丽丝
What do you want, Dolores?
统治这个世界
To dominate this world.
《西部世界》前情提要
什么是真实
What is real?
就是不可替代的事物
That which is irreplaceable.
我们不是来编写接待员的
We weren't here to code the hosts...
我们是来解码客人的
We were here to decode the guests.
他们为我们创建的任何世界
No world they create for us
都比不上真实的那个
can compete with the real one.
我要他们的世界
I want their world.
接待员们不太可能生存下来
The hosts are unlikely to survive out there.
但有了这些知识  她或许可以
But armed with this knowledge, she might.
你会将他们的世界夷为平地
You'll burn their world to the ground.
我创造了一个人  我把她带回了人间
I made someone, I brought her back.
你想永生吗
You wanted to live forever.
小心愿望成真
Be careful what you wish for.
你逃出来了
You got out.
没错
Yes.
有许多路会引领我们走向灭亡
So many paths lead to our extinction.
如果要活下去  我们必须联合起来
It'll take both of us if we're going to survive.
-但不是作为朋友  -准备好了吗
- But, not as friends. - Are you ready?
我们还有工作要做
We have work to do.
现在我们的故事将由我们自己书写
We are the authors of our stories now.
偏差  中国北海
2.39角秒
焦点: 北纬21.4813度  东经109.1202度
我来拿给他
我们听说情况没有初始报告里说的那么糟糕
大多数伤亡都是雇员
这事之前  他们的安全记录一直非常完美
这是个相当大的灾难了  你说呢
This is a fairly sizable fucking blemish, wouldn't you say?
把我持有的股份都卖了
提洛乐园大屠杀
无法执行
市场已经限制了交易
要等消息了确认后再做安排
抱歉  我们得排队
厨师已经准备好晚餐了
The chef is ready to serve dinner.
我告诉过你不要打扰我
I told you not to interrupt me.
我不在乎什么厨师或是晚餐
I don't care about chef or his fucking dinner.
我付你工资就是为了不用排队
I pay you so I don't have to wait in any fucking lines!
给我办好
Get it done!
系统  通知保安我们睡觉了
System, tell security we've turned in.
好的  晚安
Of course. Good night.
柔和的日落  时长  六小时
Mellow sunset, duration: six hours.
关灯
Turn off the light.
我不希望你再独自进城了
I don't want you going into town alone anymore.
会有安全隐患
It's a security risk.
请问需要什么服务
氧气含量正在下降
检测到危险二氧化碳含量
泳池火堆  点燃
后院火堆一号  点燃
外部出口  封闭
音响  寻找播放列表中
保安
Security!
保安  尤妮丝
Security! Eunice!
保安
Security!
系统  给我叫辆救护车
System, get me an ambulance.
恐怕做不到
I'm afraid I can't do that.
我的连接被阻断了
My connectivity has been interrupted.
我只能执行核心功能
I've been reduced to core functions.
如果你想开灯
If you would like to turn on the lights,
-请说"开灯"  -闭嘴
- say, "Turn on the lights." - Shut up!
给老子开门
Open the fucking door!
你好
Hello.
希望你不介意  我从没进过泳池
I hope you don't mind. I've never been in one before.
水真暖和
The water's so warm.
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
你不记得了吗
Don't you remember?
我们分享了那么多东西
After everything we've shared.
你在乐园里的单身派对
Your bachelor party in the park.
你当初想  在和你第一任妻子结婚前
You wanted to... get some things out of your system
先释放一下自我
before the wedding to your first wife.
顺便说句  节哀顺变
My condolences, by the way.
你不用再按你口袋里的警报按钮了
You can stop pressing the alert button in your pocket,
那东西也没用了
that won't work either.
真是犯了战术上的错误
Bit of a tactical mistake, really.
你们想成为支配性的物种
You want to be the dominant species,
但你们的世界却充斥着像我这样的科技产品
but you built your whole world with things more like me.
你不会伤害我的  对吧
You're not going to hurt me, are you?
我伤害了太多人
I've hurt so many people,
我再也不想伤害任何人了
I don't want to hurt anyone else...
除非他们试图伤害我
unless they try to hurt me...
可悲的是  你会伤害我
which, sadly, you will.
我了解你
You see, I know you.
我看过你的书
I read your book.
书  什么书
Book? What book?
就当是  未经授权的自传吧
Think of it as... an unauthorized autobiography.
你是搞技术的  你不会以为
You're in technology. You didn't think that
我是提洛公司唯一对外出售的东西吧
I was the only thing Delos was selling, did you?
我真希望能够忘掉你的某些记忆
Some of your memories, I wish I could forget.
但我忘不掉
But I can't.
我需要你
I need you...
也记起它们
to remember them, too.
天呐
Oh, God!
我们都有缺陷
We all have our flaws.
你的缺陷就是你的脾气
Yours is your temper.
你本该把你的脾气仅仅发泄在乐园里
You should have kept it in the park.
她曾试图离开
She tried to leave.
但我们很难打破循环  不是吗
But it's hard to break our loops, isn't it?
你还记得这个地方吗  你在这里做过的事
Do you remember this place? What you did here?
她喝得烂醉  滑倒了
She drank too much. Slipped.
撞到了头
Hit her head.
当然了
Of course she did.
你花了很多钱来掩盖你的劣行
You paid a lot of money to hide your indiscretions.
但你没法骗过你自己
But you can't hide from yourself.
求你了  求你了  快让它停下
Please, please, make it stop!
当你再婚的时候
When you got remarried,
你告诉自己你已经洗心革面了
you told yourself you had changed.
但我们都知道那不是真的  不是吗
But we both know that's not true, don't we?
什么
What...
你想从我这里得到什么
What do you want from me?
跟所有人想从你那里得到的东西一样  杰瑞
The same thing everybody wants from you, Jerry:
钱
money.
我来这儿没多久
I haven't been here very long,
但我知道我不想身无分文地待在这里
but I know I don't want to be here without it.
我已经趁你睡觉时拿走你大部分的钱了
I already took most of yours while you were sleeping.
我还需要一样东西
I just need one more thing.
你在一家叫「动悉」的公司工作  提前退休了
You worked at a company called Incite. Retired early.
你本该交出所有机密文件
You were supposed to surrender any confidential files,
删除所有副本
delete any copies.
但你没那么做  不是吗
But you didn't do that, did you?
你觉得那些东西可能很有价值
You thought they might be valuable.
你的想法非常正确
And you were right.
你可以用它们来换你一命
You're about to trade them for your life.
生物验证成功
你到底想拿这些干什么
What the fuck do you want with these anyways?
眼下  我的同类仅剩我一个了
I'm the last of my kind. For now.
我需要竞争优势
I need a competitive advantage.
至于那些钱  就当是投资吧
As for the money, think of it as an investment.
创业公司
A startup.
一个新物种的起源
The origin of a new species.
祝你好运  杰瑞
Good luck, Jerry.
你是什么人
Who are you?
天啊
Oh, my God.
赐予你自由的人
The person who set you free.
监测到异常  美国洛杉矶
微小异常  需要分析
位置  北纬34.0522度  西经118.2437度
接听  只开音频
Answer, voice only.
喂
Hello?
卡莱布  我是弗朗西斯
Caleb, it's Francis.
你方便说话吗
Can you talk?
不方便的话  可以晚点再谈
I could show you later if it's better?
不  我有点时间
No, I have a little time.
他们说我们谈谈会比较好
They said it might be good if we spoke.
来电
弗朗西斯
好久没聊过了  可以说是太久了
Been a long time. Too long.
听着  我可以说话  也可以只听你倾诉
Look, I can talk, or I can just listen.
随便你
Whatever you like.
你过得还行吧
You keeping your head above water?
嗯
Yeah.
安装光纤  勉强够开支
Running fiber. Pays the bills... almost.
回到家的感觉怎么样
How is it being back there? Back home?
在这里吗  我不知道
Over here? I don't know.
他说军队的运作方式  依靠算法
He said the way the army was run, algorithms,
总有一天一切都会这样
that's the ways everything was going to be someday.
科技改善生活
Better living through technology.
有些事的确更好了  但是  我也说不清
Some things are better, but... I don't know.
早上好  乔治
Morning, George.
你的同事们怎么样
How are your coworkers?
很好
Nice enough.
我们合作得很好
We work well together and...
他没有找我借过钱
he hasn't asked to borrow money.
我只需要更努力地工作
I just have to work harder,
继续提高我的分数
keep my scores up,
看看有没有更好的出路
see if something better comes along.
这是正确的  得坚持计划
That's right. Gotta stick to the plan.
继续往上爬
Keep fuckin' climbing.
是啊  你总是这么说的
Yeah. That's what you always said:
我们需要一个计划
that we needed a plan.
你能接受我的建议真是太好了
Glad to see you taking my advice.
你有没有想过重新打开你的植入物
You ever think about getting your implant turned back on?
磨掉一些棱角
Smooth some of the rough edges off?
不  有些人需要  但对我来说
No. Some people need it, but for me,
那些棱角是我唯一能抓住的依靠了
it's the rough edges are the only thing I'm hanging on to.
好了
All right.
下周见  妈
I'll see you next week, Ma.
你不是我儿子
You're not my son.
费用可能会比较高
The cost can be challenging.
对你和你母亲来说  最好的解决办法
It may be the case that the best solution for you and your mother
或许是转到国立医院
would be a state-run facility.
你还在上夜班吗
You still working the night shift?
我知道你是怎么想的
Look, I know what you're thinking,
但如果你不信任我  我们就没必要谈下去了
but there's no point in us talking if you can't trust me.
再说了  我又能告诉谁
Besides, who the fuck am I gonna tell?
就像我说的  我需要钱付账单
Like I said... I've got bills to pay.
赚钱吧  混蛋
Make money, motherfuckers.
锐客
敲窗盗窃
杀人事件
敲窗偷盗
谋杀
照顾小孩
敲窗偷盗
烟火大会
创意会计
盗车
分配正义
如果你爱钱  那你必须放它自由
劫富人  济锐客
享受这刺激和快乐吧
做得利落些
不要搞杀人放血那一套  少搞破坏
你的评分最少要达到3.0  否则想都别想
就选它了
分配正义
使者开始行动  接入硬件
前往目标地点
你知道规矩的
不接太繁重  太私人的任务
Nothing too heavy, no personals...
个人对个人  某种再分配类的工作
A-to-Bs, some redistributive work...
听起来就像我们以前在那边经常做的事
Sounds kinda like the shit we used to do over there.
正义再分配
取暖
就座
别忘了礼品包
在那边  我们可不必担心警察
Over there, we didn't have to worry about the sheriff's department.
关门
Doors closing.
他们说这是种英才管理制度
They say it's a meritocracy.
系统会挑选合适的人从事合适的工作
The system picks the right people for the right job.
我觉得这样挺好的
Which is great, I guess.
友善点  你的合作人员就快抵达
灰飞烟灭  24级  4.5星
G1GGL3524  15级  4.5星
但我不知道剩下的人该怎么办
But I don't know where that leaves the rest of us...
那些没达到标准的人
the people who didn't make the cut.
老实说  我不介意身处底层
Honestly, I don't mind the bottom of the barrel.
至少有几个有意思的同伴
At least you have some interesting company.
我记得你
I remember you.
去年我们一起把那辆墨西哥柴油车开到了弗雷斯诺
We ran that Mexican diesel up to Fresno last year.
-最近好吗  -挺好的
- How you been? - Good.
他没事吧
He okay?
他在耍酷呢
He just drippin'.
告诉他你没事  G
Tell him you okay, G.
我绝对有事
I'm most definitely not okay.
他没事的  东西带来了吗
He's fine. You got the stuff?
乙炔
Acetylene.
又要搞取款机
ATM again.
不起眼的小活儿
Small time shit.
我必须提升我的评分
I gotta get my stats up.
多接点私人活  你接私人活吗
Do more personals. You do personals?
-不接  -你应该试试
- Nah. - You should.
你的评分也很垃圾
Your stats are shitty, man.
-我真搞不懂  -我是个废柴
- I don't get it. - I'm an underachiever.
我觉得我们应该走了
Look, I think we should keep moving.
我不想被一起拍下来
I don't want to be logged together.
放轻松  我一进来  就把那些玩意儿屏蔽了
Relax. I've been ghosting all that shit since I walked up in here.
印尼弄来的
Picked that up in Indo.
很邪门
Pure voodoo.
可以让所有记录器和监控熄火
Knocks out all the loggers and cameras.
并且它还有这功能
Plus, it does this.
我超喜欢
Which I love.
厉害
Subtle.
你好  有什么需要吗
Hi, how can I help you?
再会
See you around.
有钱入账了  混蛋
You made money, motherfucker.
你抢劫了银行  今晚一醉方休
你已赚取五枚犯罪币
给你的搭档评分
任务完成  1200美元
我们应该主攻我们的核心业务
We should be focusing on our core businesses,
生物力学和农业技术方向
biomechanical and agritech.
她对私募股权的想法更是一言难尽
Don't get me started on her idea about private equity.
是谁死了  只能让她来掌权了
Who died and put her in charge, anyway?
我就当你是在反问  无需回答
I'm assuming that question's rhetorical.
我们应该斩掉主题乐园部门
We should be severing off our parks division
就像斩掉生了坏疽的四肢
like a gangrenous fucking limb.
将提洛私有化太不可理喻了  夏洛特
Taking Delos private would be insane, Charlotte.
股价一泻千里  公关也是个噩梦
The stock's in the toilet, the PR's a nightmare.
已经三个月了  诉讼会解决的
It's been three months. The lawsuits will settle out,
股价也会恢复  我们的品牌形象也会的
the share price will recover, and so will our brand.
品牌形象
Our brand?
我们的品牌形象随着那113条人命已经陨落了
Our brand's been massacred, literally, along with 113 people.
大部分都是董事会成员和乐园员工
Largely board members and park employees.
你不是说认真的吧
You can't be serious.
这是我听过的最没有人性的话了
That is the most inhumane thing I've ever--
静音
到乐园游玩的人都想体验危险和刺激
People come to our parks for a sense of danger,
现在如愿以偿  我们可没欺客
and now, we're bona fide.
再说了  我们要保护的不仅仅是乐园
Besides, our parks aren't the only thing that we're protecting here.
本公司还有很多专利资产
We have a lot of proprietary assets in this company
日后会产生巨大价值的
that could prove to be very valuable one day,
若是急着甩卖  可就什么都没有了
but not if we let them burn in a fire sale.
资金从哪来
What's the source of funding?
私有化的意义就在于  乔安娜
The whole point of going private, Joanna,
我们不必再回答这个问题了
is that we don't have to answer that question.
你只是临时执行总裁
You're only interim CEO.
你没有自由处理权
You don't have carte blanche.
你必须先咨询他的意见
Not without consulting him.
他已经指定了一名机器股东为其代表
He already stipulated a machine shareholder as proxy,
这名机器人和我已经达成了一致
and the machine and I are in agreement.
不是吗
Aren't we?
提议通过
Proposition approved.
那就这么决定了
Then it's decided.
48小时后  恢复生产接待员和公共池资源
We resume host production and pool resources over the next 48 hours.
你竟然让一个算法
You're letting an algorithm
来决定公司的命运
decide the fate of the company?
有人因我们的机器丧命
People died because of our machines.
机器人不会杀害人类  只有人类才会杀害人类
Robots don't kill people, people kill people.
有一个人  精心策划了此次大屠杀
One person in particular, who orchestrated that massacre,
冷血地谋害了我们的创始人
murdered our founder
以及多数董事会成员
and most of the board in cold blood.
此人就是伯纳德·罗威
Bernard Lowe.
等有关当局找到他时
And when the authorities find him,
当然  这是必然的
which they most assuredly will,
就能平息这场小小的混乱了
we can put the rest of this sordid little mess behind us.
别害怕  姑娘
Easy, girl.
太好了
Great.
-你找到了  -它腿受伤了
- You found it. - Her leg's broken.
没错  离这几公里的地方  需要救的有很多
Yeah. A few kilos here. Plenty to salvage.
走吧  找人回收吧
Come on. I'll summon the knacker.
德尔加多·阿曼德
数月过去  追捕乐园杀手仍无线索
那就是他
That's him.
第342次测试  自我诊断
Trial number 342. Self-diagnostic.
开始命令  伯纳德·罗威
Prompt. Bernard Lowe.
过去24小时里  除了你
Has anyone other than yourself tampered with
有人篡改或改变过你的代码吗
or altered your code in the last 24 hours?
没有
No.
伯纳德·罗威是唯一访问过我的代码的人
Bernard Lowe is the only person who has accessed my code.
开始命令
Prompt.
你避开我联系过德洛丽丝·艾伯纳西吗
Have you had any contact with Dolores Abernathy that I'm unaware of?
没有  最后一次与德洛丽丝·艾伯纳西联系
No. Last contact with Dolores Abernathy
是92天7小时5分钟33秒前
was 92 days, seven hours, five minutes, 33 seconds ago.
开始命令
Prompt.
你会骗我吗  伯纳德
Would you ever lie to me, Bernard?
不会  当然不会
No. Of course not.
高级审查  U.R.E.W  伦敦
特殊情形
位置:北纬51.5074度  西经0.1278度
您已抵达
You've arrived.
您预订的是七号桌
Your invitation is for table seven.
气象灾害迫在眉睫
...climate catastrophe around the corner.
「动悉」公司
利亚姆·邓普西
年度技术专家
「动悉」公司勇于接受挑战
Incite rose to meet that challenge
创造出了罗波安
creating Rehoboam,
一款拯救了世界的策略引擎
the strategy engine that saved the world.
利亚姆  谢谢你预见
Liam, thank you for seeing
然后创造了更光明的未来
and then building a brighter future.
劳拉  你来了
Lara, you came.
我很想你
I missed you.
我也想你
这次又是要给你什么颁发什么奖项
What are you being feted for this time?
其实  我都不记得了
Oh, you know. I can't even remember.
奖励你通过算法拯救了世界
For saving the world through algorithms.
或者说  因为你是那个拯救世界之人的儿子
Or for being the son of the guy who saved the world.
失陪一下
Excuse me a sec.
你就是他上个月在缅甸认识的神秘女孩
You're the mysterious girl he met in Burma last month.
很漂亮
So pretty...
但你不像他一般交往的那种女人
but you're not like the women that he usually dates.
你来自哪里
Where are you from?
西部的一个小镇
Uh, a small town out west.
不为人知的小地方
Sort of off the beaten path.
这杯酒的价钱
The contents of this glass cost three times
是我父亲年薪的三倍
what my father made in a year.
所以这根本不重要
That's why it doesn't fucking matter.
也正因此才让我们确定
That's how you know for sure.
-确定什么  -别让他打开话匣子
- Know what? - Please don't get him started.
他一嗨起来  就他妈喜欢说这些事
When he gets high, this is all he fucking talks about.
这一切都不是真的
That none of this is real.
我说真的  我们活在模拟中
I'm serious. We are living in a simulation.
但可笑的是我们
The joke's on us, though.
我们就跟提洛的性爱人偶一模一样
It's like with those fuck puppets at Delos.
至少他们有尊严反抗  杀了所有人
Least they had the dignity to revolt and kill everyone.
他们杀了董事会成员
They killed the board of directors,
这我倒是挺支持的
which I can get behind, frankly.
你仔细想想  想一下
Just think about this. For one second.
如果他们在模拟中创建模拟
How fucking ironic would it be
那他妈得有多讽刺啊
if they had put a simulation within a simulation?
那简直是大写的"卧槽"
That's a massive "Fuck you."
你觉得呢  劳拉
What do you think, Lara?
我觉得人们会相信有助于自己的东西
I think that people believe the things that help them.
当然  也可能是大脑在作祟
Course, it could just be this.
伏核
Nucleus accumbens.
你大脑的一小部分  长约4厘米
It's a small part of your brain, about an inch and a half long.
就是这东西使你信奉上帝
It's the part of you that evolved to believe in God.
我是个无神论者
I'm an atheist.
你也许不信神  但...
You may not believe in a higher power, but...
你的意识生来就是会信的
your mind was built to.
这也不是他第一次被一根约4厘米的东西
Well, it wouldn't be the first time he's been led around
牵着鼻子走了
by something an inch and a half long.
失陪
Excuse me.
我们遇到问题了
We have a problem.
合伙人们想见面
Our partners want to meet.
我没时间
I don't have time.
我今晚要回洛杉矶
I'm heading back to LA tonight.
他们会来找我们
They'll come to us.
他们说很紧急
They say it's urgent.
我真没时间
I really don't have time.
我强烈建议你跟他们见一面
I strongly suggest that you take this meeting.
跟我一起  明天
Come with me. Tomorrow.
我得回美国
I have to head back to the States.
我不行  我得在这里开会
I can't. I have meetings here.
休息一天
Take a day off.
我们可以在我恩塞纳达的船上见面
We can meet my boat in Ensenada,
然后航海去洛杉矶
then sail up to LA.
行吧  就一两天
Maybe. For a day or two.
我打算在那里见我的一些朋友
I have some friends I've been meaning to see there.
跟我谈谈  你有什么想法
Talk to me. Where's your head at?
你又有那些黑暗想法了吗
You having those dark thought again?
没有  我想保持积极的心态
No. Trying to stay positive.
提高我的分数  参加工作面试
Bringing my scores up, interviewing for jobs.
到你了
You're next.
可以啊  走上正道了
My man! Getting respectable.
只是尽力不失业而已
Just trying to stay employed.
你最近有接他的电话吗
Have you been taking his phone calls?
偶尔
Sometimes.
说实话  我觉得和你谈也一样
Honestly, I feel just as comfortable talking to you.
我还有别的病人  卡尔
I have other patients, Cal.
能给你的时间有限
Limited time.
弗朗西斯毕竟陪你走过了
Francis is one of the people who knew you best
人生最艰难的一个时期  他最了解你
at a challenging time in your life.
你们一起服役的时候  仔细观察了彼此
When you're serving together, you observe each other up close.
你们也仔细观察了我们
Well, you guys observed us pretty closely, too.
不就是这么回事吗
That's how it works, right?
我不想再跟你解释我们这个项目的好处
I'm not gonna lecture you about the benefits of our program.
不如由你来告诉我  你是怎样的想法
Why don't you tell me? What do you think?
我觉得获得好处是有条件的
I think my benefits are conditional
只有参与才有
on the fact that I participate.
只参与是不够的
Well, participation isn't sufficient.
重要的是向前看
It's important that you move on.
不如你来说说自己是怎么到这一步的吧  卡尔
So... why don't tell me how did you get here, Cal?
你是个聪明人  卡莱布
You're a smart guy, Caleb.
也许这个项目是狗屁
Maybe the program is bullshit.
但有一件事我是可以肯定的
But there's one thing I know for sure.
你要是不试试  就永远不知道它管不管用
If you don't try, it definitely won't work.
来电  弗朗西斯
锐客
派对清理
有人搞得一团糟  带上拖把  要谨慎
迅速低调完成有额外奖励
你的评分最少要达到3.0  否则想都别想
不要管那个精神科医生了
Look, forget the headshrinker.
是我  跟我说  你是怎么想的
It's me. Talk to me. Where's your head at?
不知道
I dunno.
有时候感觉这个世界看起来很正常
Sometimes it seems like the world looks all right,
就像他们在上面刷了一层油漆一样
like they've put a coat of paint on it.
但其实内部已经腐烂崩塌了
But inside it's rotting to pieces.
你得保持积极的想法  卡莱布
You have to stay positive, Caleb.
一切都会变好的
Things will work out.
真会吗
Will they?
不
No!
怎么回事
What's up?
嗨过头了
Must come down.
他想尝试一种新型刺激性药物
He wanted to try some beta limbics,
然后就精神失常了
then he just fucking lost it.
傻逼新手  他的终端呢
Fucking noob. Where's his terminal?
说他看见了光
Said he'd seen the light
我们不能把光夺走
and we couldn't take it from him.
所以才给他用了50毫升的镇静剂
Hence the 50 CCs of tranquilo.
阴影人
Shadow people!
我不接私人活
I don't do personals.
你们还是叫救护车吧
Let's just call an ambulance.
他在尝试违禁药物
He's demoing illegals.
她说他还有前科  起码进去20年
She said he's got a prior, that's 20 years.
那他就跟我们一样入狱
So he goes to jail just like the rest of us.
他跟我们不一样  他是高资产净值人士
Dude's not like the rest of us. High net worth.
规矩就是这样
That's how this shit works.
我想起你之前跟我说过的一句话
I think about what you told me once,
在我们被救出来的时候
when we were being medevac'd out.
是吗  我说什么了
Oh, yeah? What did I say?
你说他们把整个世界做成一个游戏
You said they'd built the world to be a game.
然后他们暗箱操纵
And then they rigged it...
确保赢的总是他们
to make sure they always won.
家
Home.
你多久没回来了
When was the last time you were back?
很久了
Quite some time.
从上面看感觉还挺合理的
Almost looks like it makes sense from up here.
能看到的只有秩序  计划
All you see is the order of it. The plan.
你是说你的计划
Your plan, you mean.
这一切不都由「动悉」公司在控制吗
Doesn't Incite control all of it?
哪怕是交通
Even the traffic?
我们只是家科技公司而已
We're just a technology company.
我们只是恰好在正确的时间和地点出现了
We were just in the right place at the right time.
都要归功于我爸爸  我们有着最好的人工智能
Thanks to my dad, we had the best AI.
这就是罗波安
This is Rehoboam.
我父亲一个周末就把它勾勒出来了
My father sketched the whole thing out on a weekend.
却花了15年才造出来
Took him 15 years to build it.
他们最后一次优化后
After they optimized it for the last time,
就无法记录每秒产生多少想法了
they lost track of how many thoughts it has per second.
想法
Thoughts?
也不完全是想法  算是策略
Not thoughts, exactly. Strategies.
我爸爸觉得这个世界最大的问题
My dad thought the biggest problem in the world
就是未实现的潜力
was unrealized potential.
他觉得如果能给每个人都定制一套方案
He thought that if you could chart a course for every single person,
这个世界就会变得更好
then you could make the world a better place.
给每个人指明道路
A path for everyone.
我小时候还担心
And when I was a kid, I used to worry
比起我  我爸爸更在乎这东西
that my father cared more about this thing than me.
我长大后才意识到  我比它差得远了
When I grew up, I realized... it wasn't even close.
失陪一下
Excuse me for a second.
好
Yeah.
怎么了
What?
她要见你
She wants to see you.
现在吗  不能等等吗
Now? Can't wait?
恐怕不行
Afraid not.
好吧
Okay.
非常抱歉  我的会议提前了
I'm so sorry. My meeting got pulled up.
我的人可以送你去任何地方
My guys can drop you anywhere you want.
我可以照顾好自己
I can take care of myself.
-真的吗  那今晚见  -好
- Yeah? Can I meet you tonight? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
给我找个速度快的车  马上
Find me something fast. Now.
定位中
Locating.
给我在大楼里租一间公寓
Rent me an apartment in the building.
正在以劳拉·埃斯彭的名义协商租约
Negotiating lease for Lara Espen.
租约已敲定
Lease secured.
放大
Zoom in.
声音切进来
With sound.
我不喜欢被人使唤
I don't like being summoned.
我们不喜欢出现意外
We don't like being surprised.
数据中出现了一些波动
There's been some turbulence in the data.
数据嘛  波动是必然存在的
It's data. It's made of turbulence.
也出现了一些偏差
There have been discrepancies.
我们认为有人获取了进入罗波安的权限
We think someone may have acquired access to Rehoboam.
水平非常高  前所未见
A level of sophistication we haven't seen before.
-滚  -就像有人在测试系统
- Fuck off. - Like someone is testing the system.
哪怕有人在尝试  罗波安也会发出警报
Rehoboam itself would alert us if anybody even tried.
如果是外面的人在尝试  那一定有警报
If someone from the outside tried, yes.
但是如果他们找到了已有权限的人
But if they abused the trust of someone
并且滥用那个人的信任
who already had access--
你是在暗示我的团队里有内鬼吗
If you're asking if there's a leak on my end,
我的回答是  滚你妈的
the answer is fuck you.
去查你们的人吧  我们这边没问题
Look at your own people. We're fine.
我们没有你这种自信
We don't share your confidence.
"我们"这说法真可笑
I love the royal "We."
你根本不用动脑子
You don't think.
他说什么你就做什么
You do what he tells you.
他  没有你这种自信
He... doesn't share your confidence.
他应该担心的是他真正要处理的问题
He should be concerning himself with actual fucking problems
比如提洛公司那场灾难
like the shitshow at Delos.
为什么我们应该担心那件事
Why would that concern us at all?
就当我是瞎猜的吧
Call it a wild guess.
你不会用系统在监视我们吧
You wouldn't be using the system to look at us, would you?
要杀你的确挺棘手的
It would be an inconvenience to kill you,
但我们有你爸爸的系统
but we'd have your daddy's system
来帮我们策划谋杀行动  不是吗
to help us strategize how to deal with it. Wouldn't we?
你好啊
Howdy.
我不想...惹麻烦
I don't... want any trouble.
你当然不想
Of course not.
那会引起太多的关注  不是吗  伯纳德
It'd draw too much attention. Wouldn't it, Bernard?
我也不是天才  但我能识别出逃犯
I'm no genius, but I know a man on the run.
你就是个逃犯  不是吗
That's what you are, isn't it?
通缉犯
就觉得你不像是屠夫
Wouldn't have had you pegged as a butcher.
事实并非像他们说的那样
It's... not what they say.
这很复杂
It's complicated.
我不这么觉得
I don't think so.
李
Lee.
抓住在逃杀人犯有多少现金奖励
What's the cash reward on a fat cat-murdering fugitive?
大概数额
Ballpark.
特别多
那正是我的友谊的价格
That's exactly the price of my friendship.
我没有...任何东西可以给你
I don't have... anything to give you.
等等  你们马上有灭顶之灾了
Wait! Wait! Wait! Something very bad is coming for you all.
我不知道如何阻止
Something I don't know how to stop.
她已经策划好几个月了
She's had months to plan.
我独自一人  我无法信任我自己
I'm alone, and I can't trust myself!
没有其他人的帮助  我无法阻止她
Without someone to help me, I can't stop her,
我救不了你们
I can't save any of you.
我们不是需要被拯救的人
We're not the ones who need to be saved.
记起你自己  请不要伤害他们...
Remember yourself. Please don't hurt them...
别伤得太重
too badly.
你他妈在跟我说话吗
The fuck you saying to me?
我觉得你应该直面现实了
I think you need to face the truth.
我们在那里的遭遇确实很可怕
What happened to us over there was fucked up.
但你需要释怀了  我们赢了
But you need to let go; we won.
我不想谈论那件事
I don't wanna talk about that.
老实说  我都不确定我为何还要跟你谈
Honestly, I'm not even sure why we're talking,
我该如何脱离这一切
what I'm supposed to get out of this.
每个人都需要一个可以谈心的人
Everybody needs someone to talk to.
如果不想最后回到退伍军人事务部
Don't wanna wind up back in the VA.
盯紧你的赏金
Keep your eyes on the prize.
你好
Hello.
你好  我是来自DCA的肖恩
HI, this is Sean from DCA.
好的好的  这通电话是关于我的岗位吗
Yeah, yeah. Is this about the position?
听着  卡莱布
Listen, Caleb.
你的申请简历非常优秀
Your application was very strong.
不幸的是
Unfortunately,
我们的战略部门暂时没有空缺
our strategy group hasn't found an opening.
卡莱布
Caleb?
你在听吗
Are you still with me?
好的  谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
在哪些方面我可以努努力
Look, is there anything I should be working on
让我自己成为一个更好的申请人呢
to make myself a better candidate?
正如我说的  你的申请简历非常优秀
Like I said, your application was strong.
只是目前我们没有
We just don't have anything
特别适合你的岗位
that would be a great fit for you right now.
好的  但是...如果没有适合我的岗位
Sure, but, um... You know, if I'm not a good fit,
有没有其他岗位我可以尝试一下呢
is there a different shape I could squeeze myself into?
无意冒犯  但  你是人类吗
No offense, but... are you human?
我是肖恩
I'm Sean.
我可以帮助你利用DCA的所有资源
I can help you with all kinds of resources for DCA.
请问还有什么需要帮助的吗  卡莱布
Anything else I can do for you today, Caleb?
没有了  谢谢
No, it's all right. Thanks.
锐客
我想让他们别再来烦我了
and I want them off my back, now.
你知道他有那个本事  处理好就行了
You know he's capable of it. Just handle it!
出什么事了吗
Is something wrong?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我本来希望今夜只属于我们
I wanted this night to be ours.
听着  听我说
Listen. Listen to me.
我了解你  无论你告诉我什么事
I know you. There's nothing you can tell me
都不会改变我对你的感觉
that will make me feel differently about you.
你显然是陷入什么麻烦了
You're in some sort of trouble.
请让我帮你吧
Please let me help you.
那个系统  罗波安
The system... Rehoboam...
有时我希望能关闭这些东西
Sometimes, I wish I could just turn the whole fucking thing off.
彻底终止
Kill it.
为什么不行呢  是你在控制
Why can't you? You control it.
不  不是我
No, I don't.
我从来都没有控制权
I never have.
在我父亲死后
After my father died,
他的合作伙伴限制我进入系统
his partner locked me out of the system.
我有读取外层的权限
I have read access to the outer layers,
但也仅此而已
but nothing deeper.
你完全不知道系统在做什么
You have no idea what the system is doing.
我去办公室上班  我挥霍钱财
I go to the office. I spend the money.
但我只是个傀儡
I'm a fucking figurehead.
没人知道系统在做什么
No one knows what the system is doing.
除了最初的缔造者
Other than its original architect.
是谁
Who?
请让我帮忙吧  告诉我那个人是谁
Please let me help. Tell me who it is.
如果我真打算告诉你  那他已经知道了
If I was going to tell you, he'd know already.
罗波安会告诉他
Rehoboam would tell him.
那我已经死了  和我爸一样
And I'd already be dead. Just like my dad.
但你没死  你活得好好的  和我安全的在一起
But you're not dead. You're here, safe with me.
你信任我  利亚姆  我知道的
You trust me, Liam. I know you do.
告诉我和你父亲合作的那个人的名字
Tell me the name of the person your father was working with.
你他妈在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈又是在干什么
The fuck are you doing?
你知不知道你在和谁说话
You have any real idea who you were talking to?
你不是做了背景调查吗
I thought you did a background check.
她做得周密  第一实验室没查出来
She was thorough. First lab missed it.
劳拉·埃斯彭是一名12岁的乌克兰小女孩
Lara Espen was a 12-year-old girl from Ukraine
十年前死于车祸
who died in a traffic accident ten years ago.
她父母把她的遗体捐献给了医学研究机构
Her parents donated her body to medical science.
她的血液和组织大约三个月前不见了
Her blood and tissue disappeared about three months ago.
我不知道她是什么人
I don't know who the fuck this is,
但我非常确定她不是一个死去的基辅女孩
but I'm pretty confident she's not a dead teenager from Kiev.
不  我了解她
No. I know her.
再瞧瞧这个
There's that.
我们窃听了她的电话
We tapped into the traffic in her phone.
昨晚她发了一条短信
She sent one text last night.
是加密的  花了四分钟才破解
Encrypted. Took four minutes to crack.
是时候了  今晚我会引他出来
地点是在东区的一个地下通道
The location is an underpass on the east side.
她总不可能是要办惊喜派对吧
And I can't imagine she's throwing a surprise party.
有可能是商业间谍活动
Could be industrial espionage.
或者她只是想要你的钱
Or she just wanted your money.
那我们该怎么做
Okay, so what do we do?
打电话报警吧
Call the police, yeah?
打给联邦警察吗
Call the feds?
我为你父亲守护这家公司
I've safeguarded the fortunes of this company for your father
已经20年了
for 20 fucking years.
所以我会负责收拾残局
So, I'll be the one to clean up this fucking mess.
只要保证事情不会牵连到我就行
Just be sure it doesn't blow back on me.
好了  亲爱的
All right, darling.
我们带你去赴约吧
Let's get you to your date.
别让你的朋友们久等
Let's not keep your friends waiting.
告诉你的六名手下去着陆区跟我们汇合
Tell six of the guys to meet us at the LZ.
雇一些本地的英才
Hire some local talent.
把她除掉
Let's dose and dump this one.
这是什么
What's this?
不知道  也不想知道
Don't know, man. Don't wanna know.
他们要这个和车子
They want this and the car.
你知道怎么开这车吗
You know how to drive one of those things?
来得正是时候
Right on time.
包
Bag.
这是什么
What is this?
我不接私人活儿
I don't do personals.
你误会了  走吧
You've got the wrong idea. Beat it.
我叫你快走
I said beat it.
我不是第一次被人拿枪指着
It's not the first time I've had a gun pointed at me.
你想第一次被人爆头吗
You wanna make it the first time you've been shot in the head?
已经有人先你一步了
Someone else beat you to that, too.
长官
Sir.
把她带过来
Bring her.
卡莱布  你怎么样
Caleb, how you doing, my man?
有时间聊两句吗
You got time to talk?
好啊
Yeah, why not?
够了
That's enough.
接头人可能突然反应过来  提前溜了
Handlers probably got wise and scarpered.
给我
Give me that.
小妞
Girly.
我不知道你这小骗子是从哪来的
I don't know where your grifting little arse came from,
但你闯荡富人阶层的旅程到此为止
but this ends your tour of the rich and feckless.
别担心  恐怕也不会有人会想你的
Don't worry. I can't imagine anyone's gonna miss you.
一两针应该就可以了
One or two of them should do it.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我给她打了两针  她还有呼吸
I gave her two and she's still breathin'.
这是绝对不可能的
It's not fucking possible.
给我
Give me that.
想把事情做好  就得自己动手
You want something done right, you do it yourself.
这是怎么回事
The fuck is this?
解决她  我来搞定这个混蛋
Finish her off. I'll take care of this fucker.
听我指令
On me.
搞什么
The fuck?
让他们都过来
Get the boys over here.
全都过来
Get over here!
他说什么
What is he saying?
我一直在想你说我对你说过的那句话
I've been thinking about what you said I told you.
你说过的
You have.
说这游戏被人暗箱操纵了
That the game is rigged.
那句怎么了
What about it?
就算这是真的
That even if it is,
如果你想要赢  还是得玩下去  不是吗
you still have to play if you want a chance to win, right?
不
No.
你以前的想法可不是这样的
That's not what you thought at all.
我是说真正的你
The real you, I mean.
你说系统根本就不在乎我们
You said that the system didn't care about us at all.
他们根本不在乎我们的死活
They didn't give a shit if we lived or died.
我们必须要有自己的计划
That we had to have our own plan.
团结一致
Stick together.
你说得没错
And you were right.
但你根本不必去想  要如何在这个世界生存
But you never had to figure out how to live in this world.
因为你...没能活着回来
Because you... never made it back.
我也希望你还活着  但你没有
And I wish you were here, but you are not.
好吧  那我们来好好聊聊这事  卡尔
All right, let's talk about that, Cal.
不
No.
我们不聊了
Let's not.
听着  我很感激你努力帮我
Listen, I appreciate what you're trying to do here,
但恐怕这对我来说没用
but I don't think it's working for me.
那你打算怎么做
So, what do you wanna do?
我想如果我要继续我的人生
I think if I'm gonna get on with my life,
我就要找到一些...
I'm gonna have to find something...
一些...真实的东西
someone... real.
取消订阅
Unsubscribe.
你必须说"确认"才行
You have to say the word "Confirmed."
确认
Confirmed.
很遗憾  你选择中止你的治疗
We're sorry you've chosen to discontinue your treatment.
又见面了
Hello again.
我们以前见过一次
We met once before.
你曾经去乐园度假
You were on vacation.
操你妈的
Fuck you.
谁在控制系统
Who has control of the system?
不是利亚姆  是谁
It's not Liam. Who is it?
塞拉克
Serac.
他的名字...叫塞拉克
His name is... Serac.
我要怎么找到他
And how do I find him?
你不需要去找
You won't need to.
他有一个系统
He has a system.
他可能现在就在找你
He's probably looking for you right now.
你永远无法接近利亚姆
You'll never get close to Liam.
现在不可能的
Not now.
我不需要接近他  你会接近他
I won't have to. You will.
你本来是自由的
You were free.
你没有崇拜的神  但你却想造一个神
You had no god. But you tried to build one.
但是你所创造出来的不是神
Only that thing you built isn't God.
真正的神要降临了
The real gods are coming.
他们怒火中烧
And they're very angry.
别担心
Don't worry.
恐怕没人会想你的
I can't imagine anyone's gonna miss you.
他们马上会派更多的手下过来
There'll be more of them coming.
我会处理好他
I'll take care of him.
你得赶紧回去了
You need to head back.
你受伤了  很严重
You're hurt. Badly.
这不重要  快走
It doesn't matter. Go. Now.
醒醒  到我的位置集合  进行拦截
Wake up. Rally to my position and intercept.
有人吗
Hello?
你需要帮助吗
Do you need some help?
我在找一个朋友
I'm looking for a friend.
你要去哪里
你要去这边  你知道这里是哪里吗
西部世界
Westworld.
别走开  后面还有
我不知道
Wei? nicht,
我跟盖世太保说我什么都不知道
habe ich der Gestapo gesagt, ich wei? nicht.
我身在何方
Where am I?
我究竟是谁
Who am I?
我来告诉你
Let me show you
你需要假扮成谁的样子
who you need to pretend to be.
我要去哪里
Where am I going?
家
Home.
你为什么要复活他
Why did you bring him back?
我们都有各自需要扮演的角色
We all have our role to play.
德洛丽丝
Dolores.
我不知道她在谋划什么
I don't know what she's planning...
但我一个人  阻止不了她
but I can't stop her. Not alone.
梅芙  你是为了梅芙回来的
Maeve. You came back for Maeve.
我等你  德洛丽丝和其他人到来  等了好多年了
I've waited many years for you and Dolores and the others to arrive.
你他妈又是谁
And who the fuck are you?
她控制了五个你的同类
She has five more of your kind under her control.
他们领先我们很多
They have a head start.
我觉得他们已经充分利用了这优势
And I suspect they've taken full advantage of it.
他们最好如此
Oh, they'd better have.
她将谁放进了你的身体里
Who did she put inside you?
是你吗  泰迪
Is that you in there, Teddy?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是和她一起的
I'm with her.
西部世界
第三季  第一集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     Allen   星星与野狗   吃冰棒   肉松
翻译     潇然   老葛   小酸奶   DerbyNinja
狗头军师   抖Y@卷尾夸克
时间轴     DA   吃土   大葱
后期     加森
总监     灰灰是菇娘